classified88.com 2007-07-04

# Malaysian classifieds for properties, automobiles, jobs, and more - Privacy Policy

**Classifieds _88_** takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This policy covers how **Classifieds _88_** treats personal information that **Classifieds _88_** collects and receives, including information related to your past use of **Classifieds _88_** products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that **Classifieds _88_** does not own or control, or to people that **Classifieds _88_** does not employ or manage. In addition, certain **Classifieds _88_** associated companies have their own privacy statements. 

**Information Collection and Use**

      **General**

  * **Classifieds _88_** collects personal information when you register with **Classifieds _88_** , when you visit **Classifieds _88 _** pages or the pages of certain **Classifieds _88_**  partners, **Classifieds _88_** may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with **Classifieds _88_** and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your [ IP address](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/ip/details.html), **Classifieds _88_** [ cookie](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html) information, and the page you request. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * **Classifieds _88_** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with **Classifieds _88_** under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help **Classifieds _88_** communicate with you about offers from **Classifieds _88_** and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of **Classifieds _88_** 's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if **Classifieds _88_** is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, **Classifieds _88 _** will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 
    * **Classifieds _88_** does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

**Cookies**

  * **Classifieds _88_** may set and access **Classifieds _88_** 's ** __**  [cookies](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html) on your computer. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** lets [ other companies](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/adservers/details.html) that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to **Classifieds _88_** 's cookies. 
  * **Classifieds _88_** uses [ web beacons](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/beacons/details.html) to access **Classifieds _88_** cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with **Classifieds _88_**  products and services. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

      **General**

  * You can edit your [ **  Classifieds** ** _88_** account information](http://edit.yahoo.com/config/eval_profile?.src=&.intl=us&.done=privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us), including your [ marketing preferences](http://subscribe.yahoo.com/showaccount), at any time. 
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the **Classifieds _88 _**service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the **Classifieds _88_** Newsletter, that are considered part of your **Classifieds _88_** account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * **Classifieds _88_** may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your **Classifieds _88 _** account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please complete a feedback form

Effective Date:  12-December-2005
